Paul test testing.testing
Stage
Paul test
2012-2014
Stage
testing.testing
20 Linear feet
- Series 1
  - http://14thandyou.blogspot.com/, 2007-2012 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General
    Neighborhood news, events and opinion blog, sometimes covering topics outside of the scope of Logan Circle.
  - http://admoblog.com/, 2010-2017 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Personal musings regarding Adams Morgan, greater Washington DC and other topics.
  - http://anacostianow.blogspot.com/, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Community information and musings on the Anacostia neighborhood.
  - http://blog.inshaw.com/, 2003-2017 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    An opinionated blog relaying community events, news, personal anecdotes, and history.
  - http://bloomingdaleneighborhood.blogspot.com/, 2005-2017 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Community blog providing news and annnouncements, with a special emphasis on local businesses.
  - http://brooklandbridge.com/, 2012-2017 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Neighborhood news and announcements, business profiles and miscellaneous posts about Brookland.
  - http://distcurm.blogspot.com/, 2010-2014 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Opinionated blog offering information and musings on life in DC.
  - http://eckingtonblog.blogspot.com/, 2006-2010 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Neighborhood announcements, observations and opinions from one Eckington resident.
  - http://eckingtondc.blogspot.com/, 2007-2009 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Community announcements, information, opinions, and musings for Eckington and the surrounding area.
  - http://fairfaxvillage.blogspot.com/, 2009-2014 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Community updates and personal musings on Fairfax Village life.
  - http://frozentropics.blogspot.com/, 2004-2017 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Community news, events, and announcements for the Trinidad, H Street, and the surrounding North Capitol Hill area
  - http://gloverparkdc.blogspot.com/, 2009-2015 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Community news and events
  - http://leftforledroit.com/, 2009-2016 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    LeDroit Park news and event announcements.
  - http://lifeontheedgewood.blogspot.com/, 2010-2016 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Community news, events, and announcements. Includes a short Edgewood Business Directory.
  - http://loganupdates.blogspot.com/, 2005-2011 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Neighborhood news and events.
  - http://newcolumbiaheights.blogspot.com/, 2008-2017 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Neighborhood news, restaurant reviews, and event anouncements.
  - http://petworthnews.blogs.com/, 2004-2010 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Petworth Community news and announcements.
  - http://pqliving.com/, 2006-2017 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Neighborhood news and events and condo listings, written by several different authors.
  - http://princeofpetworth.blogspot.com/, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    News and personal musings regarding Petworth, Columbia Heights, the 14th Street Corridor and surrounding DC neighborhoods.
  - http://stopblogandroll.blogspot.com/, 2005-2008 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Neighborhood news and updates for the Woodridge and Brookland communities
  - http://strongholddc.blogspot.com/, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Blog offering community news and event information.
  - http://the42bus.blogspot.com/, 2007-2016 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - http://thebrightwoodian.blogspot.com/, 2010-2012 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Brightwood community news and information. Features a Ward 4 local business guide.
  - http://thetottenlife.blogspot.com/, 2010-2013 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Community news, events, and updates for the North Michigan Park, Brookland and Fort Totten area. Special tab for DC neighborhood and ANC 5a maps.
  - http://www.bygonebrookland.com (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - http://www.crestwood-dc.org/ (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Citizens Association blog covering community news, events and history
  - http://www.foresthillsconnection.com/, 2012-2017 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Neighborhood news and lifestyle-magazine for the Forest Hills community.
  - http://www.jdland.com/dc/index.cfm, 2003-2017 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Community information and updates about the Navy Yard area. Includes a special page on Nationals Ball Park, a project directory, and a photo archive.
  - http://www.mvtriangleblog.com/, 2008-2016 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    News, updates, and events regarding Mt. Vernon and adjacent communities, as well as community real estate information and listings.
  - http://www.popville.com/, 2007-2017 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    New and current version of the Prince of Petworth blog. News, events, and updates from all of DC's neighborhoods. Shows special attention to DC restaurants.
  - http://www.swtlqtc.com/, 2008-2017 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Community information, announcements, and updates on Southwest DC. Special emphasis is given to neihgborhood changes and development. Includes a development map and a tab providing information on the Southwest Waterfront Redevelopment.
  - http://www.titanoftrinidad.com/, 2012-2014 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Sometime satirical blog providing community news and announcements for the Trinidad neighborhood. Includes an anonymous news tip form.
  - https://clevelandpark2.wordpress.com/, 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Community news and events in Cleveland Park.
  - https://friendshipheightsgirl.wordpress.com/page/2/, 2009-2011 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Blog documenting the adventures and experiences of a Friendship Heights resident.
  - https://gatewaytothecitydc.com/, 2013-2017 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Community news, events, and announcements, authored by the ANC commissioner
  - https://georgetownmetropolitan.com/, 2008-2017 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Neighborhood photos, updates, news, events, and personal musings. Blog shares name with a 19th Century Georgetown newspaper.
  - https://mtpleasantdc.wordpress.com/, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Mt. Pleasant events, announcements, business reviews, experiences and opinions as relayed by two residents and friends
  - https://newbrightwoodianblog.com/, 2012-2017 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Brightwood community news and information.
  - https://parkviewdc.com/, 2013-2017 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Neighborhood news and events